Hello.
In this next lecture, we're going to be setting up the logic for our mushroom blueprint.
If you open up the mushroom blueprint and head over to the event graph, we can delete event.
We can play an event active again, an overlap and into free space.
If you right click and look for add custom event and call this handle rotation.
So authentic.
Every frame we're going to be making sure our mushroom is facing our player character.
So over the authentic drag and look for handle rotation.
I'm just going to close this.
And if we head back to our Scantron blueprint, if you remember, when we handle the damage for Scantron,
we get the location of the actor that damaged it, which is our player character.
We get our authentic location.
Then we use this node called get unit direction, and it is value is less than zero.
That basically means our player character is in front of our enemy.
And so we want our enemy to face our player character.
We're going to use this node, but run it every single frame.
So our mushroom is always facing our player character.
So if we head back to our mushroom beep and we'll have handle rotation just right click and it will
get there.
Character.
And tow truck.
Okay.
And we'll get actor location then we just want to right click and get actor location and drive away
and forget unit director and hiccup two to hit then off the return value just right click and look for
split structure pin and drag off the return value from x and check to see if this is less than zero.
If this condition is true, that basically means our player character is facing towards the right of
us.
So we want our mushroom to be facing towards the right.
So I'm going to hook up from hand of rotation into here.
Then in order to make our mushroom face the right, we can just right click and look for set actor rotation
and hook up.
True to here.
If this is false, that means our player character is facing towards the left of us and so we want our
mushroom to face the left.
I'll just copy this.
And under false in Z per value of 180.
And just so that you can visually see what I mean off of the handle rotation, just drag.
Okay.
And look for print string and hook up X to here.
Now if I go to compile close this and I'm just going to drag in my mushroom here.
So I put my player character in Enemy on Layer 20.
So I put my mushroom on Layer 20.
And I'm just going to move my player character.
So he starts here and if I go play, we can see it's currently print stringing the value one.
So if I open up my mushroom blueprint.
The value one is clearly greater than the value zero.
So the condition for this branch is false.
So we make our mushroom face towards the left.
However, if I just jump over my mushroom.
This value becomes negative one.
And if I go back to my mushroom blueprint.
So negative one is clearly less than zero.
So that means this condition is true.
So we make our mushroom face towards our player character.
So if I just close this and go back to my mushroom game.
Now, our mushroom is always going to face our player character.
The next thing we're going to do is make it so our mushroom can be damaged.
Like our skeleton enemy.